I don't mean you, baby.
Hi, nothing happened, we're not going to be here, it happened.
Hi game.
Maybe I happen nothing happened. I
Took a little day off. Yeah, well, I mean I was I was on yesterday. I was on a couple times I just
You know my friends came over and we spent a lot of time
cleaning the house. Oh my god the bathroom is clean the
Vacuum the kitchen is clean everything is looking good
Why are you so fancy?
Being fussy, you miss it. Yeah, baby
All right
Yeah
How are you guys? Hey, Jamie? I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I think people were trying to check in with me. I'm sorry
I just think you know, I was I
Have my subs this morning kind of a recently woke up
I'm gonna hang out with you guys
Yeah
Don't know if my new charger came out. I might have got a new charger for my bike, but I
Don't know if it'll work. I'm just kind of dreading. Yeah, it won't
That there is a place that uh
Our bikes helps around there's a lot of bikes helps around here. I'm sure I hopefully so maybe fix them
I think they will be hi guys. How are you? Do you hear me? Okay? Hi spunky? Hi, Jamie. Hi. I'm Samantha KZ Jeff
Nick, is anybody, yeah guys, well I looked into it.
I think I have like, I think they,
I think it's that I have 75 or so memberships.
That's pretty amazing, I mean that's like,
so it's like, you know, I did have 100 at one point
because there was like gifted in that first month,
but I've had a lot of gifted this month too.
pretty much is
I think one of the major
That's one of the major sources of income sir as part of the monetization comes at that in superchats
But I did I did add a new feature today. It or yesterday it says I
Don't know it says there's some kind of gift
I don't know if you buy the gift with the points or like there's in the
Not sure it enables some kind of gift thing. So if you want to like you want to like do something
Have a form of like a little I don't know that the YouTube
Gift things I don't I don't know how you can you guys have to tell me how it looks like I can't really imagine
Despite what they said I just I just enabled it
Yeah, how are you guys how is I just have to charge I'm trying to charge this the this the headphones a little bit and
Okay, that's a little bit better the cord is so short
So, yeah, so that, that, yeah, so, that I'm pretty stoked about.
Hi, Mikey.
Hi, bud.
Yeah, I'm stoked on that.
So, I also got some, yes, but, yeah, I'm really, like, I mean, I think the, if it wasn't for
I mean, I was just like...
It's like, I did, you know how satisfying it feels to have a cleaner room and how much nicer to live a cleaner room
other than its organization and its chaos around you?
But it's so much nicer.
But it's like, I...
I need I do like realize that I don't know I forgot I've forgotten how like how important it is
So I'm gonna keep I'm gonna try to keep it up. Hey for hey page. How are you? Hi page? I thought you were on
Earlier today good for you
You heard I passed the what like a rumor that you told me you made up you made up the rumor
The house helps to make
Make
of a clean mind too, yes.
You know what?
So he came in and he wanted to,
he's like, I want to clean your bathroom.
So my tub was like,
Now that I see it clean. Oh my I'm just a bear. It's like oh my god. What do you must have thought like help help?
Oh my gosh, like my bathtub was just like so it's just we know white porcelain tub
I thought I was just it's colored permanently. I mean, I thought that was like it is just turned yell
I just you know and it was like, you know
No, oh my god, it's like he put so much so much a bleach in that Ajax
All kinds of stuff in it. You got the 19. Oh, oh
No, you hopefully did not do that
Yeah, I'm sure Doug is kidding
Nobody would nobody hopefully know we would get that many your girlfriend's boyfriend took you out you get it
he's came back to me in celebration of
You're thirsty. Oh my gosh. Well, she's a factory. That's good
Hey
Well
You know I always want to
Go to the all natural breath possible, right? Hey, Lola. Hey Lola
Hello
Yeah, so he gave me some weed too, but I already have some weed guys. I think I'm gonna quit smoking cigarettes because
It's too ridiculous. I'm already like way behind budget this week because I bought these stupid packs of cigarettes every day
It's like $25 30 dollars
Or it's like for I mean for like three packs and three packs that I bought like 30 bucks
That's a lot and it's like they're not even good. There's like I don't like the flavor. I can't get switches anymore
and
Plus I hate walking in a liquor store
Or even if I have a bike, you know
Wives makes for sure that you can't hit. Oh Doug. Come on
No, we don't want to I we I say smoke some weed though. You can actually smoke weed
Yeah
Oh my gosh, my battery's not charging as well at this moment
It's charging it's a noble Castro
Why so yeah, so yeah, what's up, dude? How are you guys? I think I can give the link to it
Have I posted the link yet? I don't know. I need to find my phone
I found my phone
Might be moving to my neck of the woods soon Wow, it'd be cool
Hey juice
Did you fake my death?
Why do you think I fake my,
I mean guys, I was not gone.
I was gone for less than a day.
What are you talking about?
There's a good song by the youth though.
You know how you heard the band that you call the youth.
And it's like, back from the dead.
Oh, also a million Martinez as a song that goes back to.
Let's see. I mean, I'm in a good mood, but I just did a lot of thinking about life and stuff.
You know, these, I see them in concert, actually. I saw these.
Oh
You don't be that much. Thank you guys. I don't know. Is there may
Here
I can't read anymore
My eyes are dismissed up. I dance to the gun play. I think there's beach in my eyes
You're not
Leech I'm sorry, it's so small is there oh, you know what I did I changed it to me like a different color hold on I
Can change it back to making it
That's her in color a lot
I did it, I hear.
Okay, I think that might help.
I just turned it, because it was on black
and it had the white lettering,
and for some reason that, so I think it's better.
You've been worried about stuff.
One of the best brands you've seen was,
this card, card.
Hugh and Podhawk is telling everyone,
I, next last night, why were they telling people that?
Q and people and pothog is like you and pothog is we're saying that pothog is is that true?
Hey Nancy, hey everybody spunky
Pothog is I'm fine. I look fine. Oh, I'm fine. I'm gonna my nice shirt. Hold on
I'm just like I have to hunch over a little bit now. I need to shave my house. It's a lot better
Trying to cut down on cigarettes and alcohol right now guys
But I'm still gonna smoke a little bit of pot
Give me my mind I sure
Yeah
Looking back in my old lab my labyrinth book. No, where have we this maze? We've gone through
It's labyrinth of life, you know, I have some old pictures
People in this book too. I have my original page drawing. I
Have my original beaded drawing. I just want to show it because I
Don't want to bend people. Yeah, there's pages. I
Don't want to tend to I'm sorry. There's pages. These are my first drawings guys. I would do a better drawing now
I just feel like I put a witch's hat and I don't think she liked it.
But I put horns on Gotti. I just do little things.
That was Paige.
This is Joker right there.
That's Joker right there.
He's like a little deep man with his big wiener.
And then that's like untragable. He's like keeping track of Joker. He's like I heard you were at the January 6
rally
Mr. Joker
And Joker's the guy, uh
Anyway
Yeah, but these are my first drawings, you know, and then this is kind of like, you know
I like adapted the Alex, but I drew another picture of Alice. It came out pretty much the exact same, you know
It's just like this the it's like evil smiling demon
This is my first stand man right there. It's like my first stand man
He did a decent job with that one
That more I don't know. I mean I do oh, yeah, I drew Q but I don't want to like mention Q. There's Q
You know, he's there. He's not that bad-looking guy
Yeah, I kind of made him look like
kind of looks
Not as like handsome as he probably is. I hope he's not offended by it. Oh, that's not
my art
Some people I look guys isn't that funny it's like some people I don't even remember
who they are because
They've disappeared and I've dried your picture of my own
Rainy day and Monday always get me
Okay
Looking at some
Words of this book.
Hey, buddy.
Oh, he said before drunk on shooting
that he would meet up with me and sleep with me.
Oh my God.
He would?
No, I don't think he's asleep with me.
He always calls me the F-A-G-G-O-T word.
Oh, you want to, you want something to thank you guys?
Here, I might have to post it a few times, so on.
Yeah, you like the carpenters?
I mean, I keep having Q back on, like I'm some idiot who keeps letting him back on and he keeps saying bad things to me.
He keeps saying, you know, he keeps saying mean things about me.
Oh look, I have a list of trees.
I don't know what this list of trees is for. I don't know.
Hold on, let me look for it.
I don't know, but I have a list of trees, guys.
Do you want to hear a list of trees?
Oh, it's a plant?
I think it's a list of plants.
No, no, okay, so yeah, it's a list of plants.
It says aspen, pistachio, magnolia, birch,
marjoram, ferns, mandrake, parsley,
bergamot, star anis, fennel,
mace, mace?
Um
Spunk Spunknard
Spaniard, I don't know mystic gum
Or mastic gum
Styrax, but these sound like this. They just don't like the names of streamers, you know
Styrax it says Styrax then
Okay, I don't know
Aluminum that says
Kara
Land that that be the uh, I can't read my own writing. Mm-hmm. Okay
I have a list of words
That have a different stuff, okay, oh, I'm sorry guys
Yeah, there's actually a spyrex Pokemon card, you know
There's actually a Pokemon. I don't know. We're not Pokemon. I don't know if it's a Pokemon
I don't really understand Pokemon. I mean, this is my this is my book. It's my own labyrinth book
It's my little little diary. I I've kept to have some
Interesting stuff right in it here
I don't think I can read some of these pages
I have a whole page with conspiracy terms.
Like I could say, conspiracy, you could say plot,
scheme, sedition, treason, cabal, Confederacy,
connivance, countermind, counterfeit, I don't know.
Just loyalty, a fix.
frame a game hook up a bunco designs
What's what's this for everyone? He's here. They're making they're making something
They're also intrigue league. Oh machinations. I have the word machinations here machinations. Yeah profidity
practice treachery trick trickery
cumplot
Cobian little game put up jib a treacherousness a collusion a racket contrivance
Oh
How's everyone doing yeah, I was trying to find something just I mean it's like I
Have this but I have a page that says tells
And it's like I these are all the things that like if these things are around it tells me something is a
Foot or a miss or something. I have pages of them
page into these tells. I'll read you maybe one page. Okay. Oh. Oh, draw me. Okay, who's
Yes, I'm sorry. I forgot about you. I mean, I didn't forget about you. I was waiting. I mean, you're always you know
You're always providing the art. I have to get my notebook. I'll be back
Okay, do you hear me
Let me see.
Okay, well, I'll put you on full screen
so I can like look at you better, hold on.
If he's gonna draw me, okay.
So, I don't know, I mean, how would,
I mean, I'm just gonna have to draw you how you look today,
but you always like look different, you know, it's like,
I mean, you look like Jamie Kennedy, basically.
I mean, that's basically it, but then you,
oh, oh, is your shirt off?
You want me to do your, okay, oh my God.
Okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no Nick. I don't think that's appropriate Nick
Show that it's not that's not real show. That's not real. I don't want it like that. No, no, no
I don't want to get poor mom guys that okay
Guys wish I should I delete the stream. Oh my god
What do you think guys
No, no, no, no, no, no, I'm ending the stream